Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, 1967-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Cassettes with Mikhashoff as performer or composer, 1967-1993, I.; Item 1-149
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 62, 16 November 1983, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Nov 16, 83 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Hall Dolby B The contents on the label list another Norgaard work but the printed program lis
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_062_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_062_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_062_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_062_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_062_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_062_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_062_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_062_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_062_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_062_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_062_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_062_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_062_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_062_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_062_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_062_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_062_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_062_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_062_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_062_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 63, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Feldman: Piano Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Dolby B Match Derivative files created: 1 (Box 2, Item 63)
    Contents: Feldman: Piano (1977)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_063_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_063_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_063_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 64, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Feldman Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Match Derivative files created: 2 (Box 2, Item 64)
    Contents: Feldman: Two pieces for three pianos; Hiller: Fantasy for three pianos
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_064_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_064_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_064_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_064_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_064_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_064_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 65, undated, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Ferneyhough Performers: James Avery, piano Recording location: Unknown location Match? Derivative files created: 1 (Box 2, Item 65)
    Contents: Ferneyhough: Lemma -- Icon -- Epigram
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_065_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_065_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_065_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 66, 12 March 1985, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Finney Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Hartt College of Music (Hartford, Conn.) Content on Side A only Order of works not stated in printed program but confirmed by listening. Match Derivative files created: 5 (Box 2, Item 66)
    Contents: Finney: Variations on a theme by Alban Berg -- Waltz (1977) -- Youth's companion -- Lost whale calf -- Nostalgic waltzes
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_066_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_066_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_066_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_066_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_066_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_066_01-05pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_066_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_066_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_066_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_066_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_066_01-05sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 67, 11 September 1988, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Foss Cto. 2: Buenos Aires Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Orquesta filarmonica de Buenos Aires; Bruno d'Astoli, conductor Recording location: Teatro Colon (Buenos Aires, Argentina) Dolby B Label on side of case: Nancarrow Lic center - there does not seem to be any Nancarrow on the tape Match Derivative files created: 1 (Box 2, Item 67)
    Contents: Foss: Piano concerto no.2
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_067_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_067_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_067_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 68, 31 October 1987, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Foss Cto. 2: Rome Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Orchestra sinfonia di Roma della RAI Radiotelevisione italiana; Harold Farberman, conductor Recording location: Auditorium del Foro Italico (Rome, Italy) includes dress rehearsal of Concierto no. 2 on side B Repeated on side 2 Derivative files created: 2 (Box 2, Item 68)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_068_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_068_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_068_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_068_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_068_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_068_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 69, 10 December 1978, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Foss/Messiaen Performers: Messiaen: Mikhashoff, piano; University Philharmonia; James Kasprowicz, conductor. Foss: UB Percussion Ensemble; Sylvia Dimiziani, soprano Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Hall Messiaen performed 10 December 1978, the Foss performed 3 December 1978 Messiaen divided over 5 tracks Derivative files created: 6 (Box 2, Item 69)
    Contents: Messiaen: Oiseaux exotiques; Foss: 13 ways of looking at a blackbird
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_069_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_069_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_069_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_069_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_069_01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_069_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_069_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_069_02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_069_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_069_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_069_01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_069_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_069_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_069_02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 70, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Gerhard Performers: Unidentified performers Recording location: Unknown location Side B label: Concerto rehearsal; Label on spine of insert: Old recording and rehearsal with Y.E.M. Derivative files created: 3 (Box 2, Item 70)
    Contents: Roberto Gerhard: Harpsichord concerto -- Canciero de Pedrell
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_070_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_070_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_070_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_070_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_070_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_070_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_070_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_070_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 71, 13 October 1991, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Golden piano Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Almeida festival (London, England) Program titled: The golden piano: Berlin matinee: Twenty-one works played and heard in Berlin in the golden Twenties. Program was previewed 6 October 1991 in Baird Hall at University at Buffalo. Contents from printed program need verification. 21 works? 01-10 is Ravel; sounds like the Antheil is omitted Derivative files created: 19 (Box 2, Item 71)
    Contents: Busoni: Klavierubung; Toch: Der Jongleur; Hindemith: Nachtstuck; Stravinsky: Chorale; Antheil: Sonata no.3; Eisler: Sonata no.1. Adagio; Wolpe: Stehende Musik; Webern: Kinderstuck und Klavierstuck; Krenek: Klavierstuck; Berg: Wirsthauswalzer; Ravel: Valse americaine; Schulhoff: Etude de jazz. Tango; Hindemith: Einleitung und Lied; Weill: Threepenny opera suite (arr. By Mikhashoff); Schoenberg: Klavierstuck; Brand: Electric pianola foxtrot; Petyrek: Wurstelprater; Gruenberg: Jazz mask; Martinu: Sketch; Bartok: Mikrokosmos; Gebhardt: Erinnerung
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_071_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_071_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_01-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_02-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_071_02-09pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_071_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_01-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_02-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_071_02-09sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 72, 8 July 1982, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Grainger. Label: Grainger 100th birthday concert Performers: Unidentified performers Recording location: New Music America (Festival) (Chicago, Ill.) Grainger 100th birthday concert Check against Grainger folder in annotated scores to identify unlisted works Derivative files created: 9 (Box 2, Item 72)
    Contents: Grainger: Molly on the shore -- String quartet -- Shepherd's hey -- Children's march
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_072_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_072_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_072_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_072_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_072_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_072_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_072_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_072_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_072_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_072_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_072_02-08pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_072_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_072_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_072_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_072_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_072_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_072_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_072_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_072_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_072_02-08sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 73, 14 November 1981, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Happy birthday Aaron and Virgil Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Anthony de Mare, piano Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Hall World première of parts of Thirteen portraits; Program entitled: Happy birthday to Aaron and Virgil inserted; continued on Tape 74 01-06 is a Prelude by Thomson - misidentified in notes as being by Copland; Copland Sonata 2 replaced by Sonata 1; Thomson piano sonata omitted? Derivative files created: 11 (Box 2, Item 73)
    Contents: Copland: Three sonnets -- Prelude -- Three moods -- Second prelude -- Petit portrait -- Thomson: Prelude -- Synthetic waltzes; Copland: Vocalise -- Piano sonata no.1; Thomson: Violin sonata no.1 -- Piano sonata no.1 -- Thirteen portraits
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_073_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_073_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_073_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_073_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_073_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_073_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_073_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_073_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_073_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_073_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_073_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_073_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_073_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_073_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_073_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_073_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_073_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_073_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_073_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_073_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_073_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_073_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_073_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_073_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 74, 14 November 1981, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Happy birthday Aaron and Virgil II Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin Recording location: University at Buffalo, Baird Hall Dolby Continuation of Tape 73 OK Derivative files created: 1 (Box 2, Item 74)
    Contents: Copland: Duo for violin and piano
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_074_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_074_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_074_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 75, undated, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Hiller Performers: Stephen Manes, piano; Frieda Manes, piano; Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University at Buffalo Dolby OK Derivative files created: 2 (Box 2, Item 75)
    Contents: Hiller: Fantasy -- Quadrilateral
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_075_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_075_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_075_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_075_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_075_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_075_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 76, 21 September 1982, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Hiller Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University at Buffalo Insert spine: Copy of master tape for recording OK Derivative files created: 1 (Box 2, Item 76)
    Contents: Hiller: Quadrilateral for piano and tape
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_076_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_076_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_076_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 77, undated, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Hiller Performers: Unidentified performers Recording location: Unknown location Note on insert indicates that order of works is as indicated in stated contents, not as stated on cassette label. OK Derivative files created: 7 (Box 2, Item 77)
    Contents: Hiller: Fantasy for 3 pianos -- Four piano pieces: Prelude; Two theater pieces; Blue triangle -- Quadrilateral -- Diabelskie skrzypce
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_077_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_077_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_077_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_077_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_077_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_077_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_077_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_077_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_077_02-05pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_077_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_077_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_077_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_077_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_077_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_077_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_077_02-05sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 78, 6 June 1982, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Holland festival: American piano Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Holland festival (Rotterdam, Netherlands) Dolby B Program entitled: American piano, repeated 10 June in Amsterdam and 13 June in Utrecht. There is no confirmation of which concert this recording represents. 18 works, 17 files. Griffes omitted Derivative files created: 17 (Box 2, Item 78)
    Contents: Cowell: Advertisement; Ives: Alcotts; Ornstein: A la chinoise; Griffes: The white peacock; Gershwin: Rialto ripples; Copland: Three moods; Antheil, George: Sonata no.3, "The death of machines"; Cowell: The banshee; Thomson: Five easy pieces; Rudhyar: Stars and sunburst; Nancarrow: Sonatina for piano; Becker: Sound piece no.5; Bernstein: Two anniversaries; Antheil: Valentine waltz; Riegger: Tone clusters; Feldman: Illusions; Hiller: Blue triangle; Barber: Fugue
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_078_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_078_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_078_02-08pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_078_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_078_02-08sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 79, 4 April 1985, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Bridgewater 4-11-85 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano and interviewee; Aileen Bridgewater, interviewer Recording location: Hong Kong Producers: Joel Delacy; Puni Rao; Anna Chilvers Derivative files created: 1 (Box 2, Item 79)
    Contents: Ailleen Bridgewater talk show: an interview of Yvar Mikhashoff by Aileen Bridgewater on Hong Kong Commercial Radio
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_079_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_079_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_079_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 80, October 1988, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Hong Kong 1988 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Hong Kong There is a long gap on Side A between the Rzewski and Curran works Studio recording with Mikhashoff announcing each work. Label: RTHK (Hong Kong Commercial Radio) Derivative files created: 12 (Box 2, Item 80)
    Contents: Glass: Modern love waltz (2 takes); Copland: Sonnet no.1 -- Sonnet no.2 -- Sonnet no.3 -- Ornstein: Afternoon in Chinatown (1 incomplete take followed by complete take); Rzewski: Piano piece no.4 (incomplete); Curran: For Cornelius Side B: Debussy: Preludes, Bk. 1. Ce qu'a vu le vent d'Ouest -- Bk. 2. Feuilles mortes -- La puerta del vino -- Minstrels -- Ondine –
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_080_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_080_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_080_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_080_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_080_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_080_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_080_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_080_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_080_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_080_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_080_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_080_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_080_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_080_02-05pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_080_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_080_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_080_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_080_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_080_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_080_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_080_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_080_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_080_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_080_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_080_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_080_02-05sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 81, 13 February 1990, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Hong Kong Inter Performers: Mikhashoff, piano and interviewee Recording location: Hong Kong Date on cassette label is '88; 1990 date from insert Derivative files created: 1 (Box 2, Item 81)
    Contents: Radio interview with Yvar Mikhashoff on RTHK (Hong Kong Commercial Radio) Commercial with excerpts from a Mikhashoff recital
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_081_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_081_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_081_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 82, 12 February 1990, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Hongkong Recital Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Hong Kong Dolby B Contents from printed program need to be verified 13 works, 11 files; Satie omitted Derivative files created: 11 (Box 2, Item 82)
    Contents: Glass: Opening -- Modern love waltz; Harrison: Waltz for E.H.; Stravinsky: Valse pour les petits lecteurs de Figaro; Satie: Deuxieme valse pour un precieux degoute; Thomson: For a happy occasion; Mikhashoff: Long eyes of earth; Debussy: Ce qu'a vu le vent d'ouest -- Feuilles mortes -- Minstrels -- Feux d'artifice; Liszt: Nuages gris; Liszt-Mikhashoff: Hungarian rhapsody no.19
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_082_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_082_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_082_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_082_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_082_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_082_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_082_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_082_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_082_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_082_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_082_01-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_082_01-11pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_082_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_082_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_082_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_082_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_082_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_082_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_082_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_082_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_082_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_082_01-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_082_01-11sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 83, 25 October 1988, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Yvar in Hong Kong II Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Hong Kong Mikhashoff announces the changes from the printed program; contents require further verification. Other works programmed were Ringvos: Study in 5 parts and Norgaard: Achilles and the tortoise OK Derivative files created: 5 (Box 2, Item 83)
    Contents: Dench: Topologies; Young Shui-ting: The tide; Ye Xiaogang: Ballade; Unidentified work; 5 Tangos
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_083_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_083_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_083_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_083_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_083_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_083_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_083_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_083_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_083_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_083_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_083_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_083_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 84, 24 October 1988, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Yvar in Hong Kong I Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Radio Television Hong Kong Feldman broken over 2 files because it started on side 1 but ended on side 2 Derivative files created: 6 (Box 2, Item 84)
    Contents: Glass: Opening; Scelsi: Quatro illustrazione; Foss: Solo; Feldman: Palais de Marais; Rzewski: Piano piece no.4
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_084_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_084_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_084_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_084_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_084_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_084_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_084_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_084_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_084_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_084_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_084_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_084_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_084_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_084_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 85, 4 November 1983, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Hopkins Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Danish Radio Symphony Orchestra; Jan Latham Koenig, conductor Recording location: Musikhuset (Aarhus, Denmark) Note in program: Very historical concert - orchestra was drunk? OK Derivative files created: 1 (Box 2, Item 85)
    Contents: Hopkins: Piano concerto, The Magic mountain
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_085_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_085_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_085_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 86, 19 August 1984, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Piano recital Havikodden Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Havikodden (Norway) Dolby B Derivative files created: 10 (Box 2, Item 86)
    Contents: McDowell: Sonata no. 3; Cage: 49 pieces; Rorem: Barcaroles; Stravinksy; Moods no. 3, 4; Selected waltzes and dances; Curran: For Cornelius; Rzewski: Piano piece no. 4
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_086_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_086_02am.wav